Full stack developer with experience in all stages of the development cycle for web projects. Practical knowledge of numerous modern technologies. Focused on front-end lately yet can work perfectly with back-end.

Visualizes the whole thing from the user's perspective to come up with ideas

Visualizes the whole thing from the user's perspective to come up with ideas and solutions for possible problems.

## **Work History**

## 2020-10 -2022-09

## **Software Developer**

Adven.Tech, Cornélio Procópio

- Worked developing web apps such as a stock management, event, e-commerce and other systems on client demand.
- Helped migrating legacy systems to modern technologies.
- Wrote clean and scalable code for both the back and front end.
- Worked with popular technologies such as Angular, React, .NET, C#, SQL and others.

## 2018-12 -2020-10

## Designer

ADRA Brasil, Brasilia

- Designed art for fundraising campaigns.
- Automated daily tasks with VBA and SQL.
- Developed a system with Laravel and Vue to help with hot meals distribution for Venezuelan refugees.

## 2017-05 -2018-07

## **Game Developer**

Roundstars, Brasília

- Worked on developing single-player and multiplayer games.
- Coded core mechanism, search algorithms and bots Als.
- Designed interfaces and arts for games.
- Wrote clean C# code for games on Unity Engine.

## **Education**

2016-01 -	Degree: Game Development
2018-06	IESB - Brasília, Brazil
2021-11 -	Postgraduate Degree: Prog. Analysis And Dev.
2022-06	Descomplica - Brazil
2021-11 -	Postgraduate Degree: Mobile App Development
2022-06	Descomplica - Brazil

## ARTUR JUNIOR

Full Stack Developer

## Contact

### **Address**

Grace Park, Dublin, Ireland

## Phone

+353 83 124 6901

### E-mail

arturcmjr@gmail.com

### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/arturcmjr

## **Portfolio**

https://arju.dev

# Technologies Highlight

- .NET
- TypeScript
- Angular
- C#
- React
- SQL
- Git

## **Essential Skills**

- Fast learner
- Self-starter
- Creative
- Critical thinking